import 'package:quizapp/entities/questions.dart';

final List<Question> questionListSubjectA = [
  Question(
    [],
    question: "qui est-il ?",
    answer: "personne",
  ),
  Question(
    [],
    question: "quel heure est-il ?",
    answer: "16h",
  ),
  Question(
    [],
    question: "de quel couleur est le ciel ?",
    answer: "bleu",
  ),
  Question(
    [],
    question: "quel est le framework ?",
    answer: "flutter",
  ),
  Question(
    [],
    question: "combien de mains avons-nous ?",
    answer: "deux",
  ),
  Question(
    [],
    question: "1+1 = ?",
    answer: "2",
  ),
];
final List<Question> questionListSubjectB = [
  Question(
    ["aze", "azeaze", "azeazeae", "16h"],
    question: "quel heure est-il ?",
    answer: "16h",
  ),
  Question(
    ["aze", "azeaze", "azeazeae", "17h"],
    question: "quel heure est-il ?",
    answer: "17h",
  ),
  Question(
    ["aze", "azeaze", "azeazeae", "18h"],
    question: "quel heure est-il ?",
    answer: "18h",
  ),
  Question(
    ["aze", "azeaze", "azeazeae", "19h"],
    question: "quel heure est-il ?",
    answer: "19h",
  ),
];
